http://www.ecd.com/privacy.aspx#cookie

Search
ECD website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
Login
ECD Home of the M.O.L.E.® Thermal Profilers | Focused on Quality, Driven by Passion
Toggle navigation
HomeSolutionsProducts Thermal ProfilersProcess Test PalletsAccessoriesContinuous MonitoringDry StorageSoftwareClose
MegaMOLE 2020
Channel Thermal ProfilerSuperMOLE Gold 26 Channel Thermal ProfilerV-MOLE3 Channel Thermal ProfilerV-MOLE Solar3 Channel Thermal ProfilerMiniMOLE rHRelative Humidity Logger WaveRIDERSimplify your Wave Solder setupOvenCHECKERReflow Process VerificationOvenRIDERConvection Reflow Oven VerificationSelectiveRIDERSelective Solder Repeatability ToolFluxometerMaximize Yields and Reduce Rework TemprobePCB Precise Sensing InstrumentThermocouplesThermal Profiler SensorsSideRIDERExpandable Profiler CarrierE-Z RIDERWave Solder Profiler CarrierReflow RIDERReflow Oven Profiler CarrierBoard CarrierPCB Board Carrier OvenSENTINELIntelligent Monitoring Solutions SD-1010 cu ft Dry CabinetSD-3030 cu ft Dry CabinetSD-48F48 cu ft Dry Cabinet MOLE MAPECD's Main Profiling Software Support Product ServicesLearning CenterRegister-MAP-SoftwareClose
Product CalibrationISO 17025 AccreditedRMA RequestReturn ECD product Support RequestHardware or Software Support FAQFrequently Asked QuestionsResourcesThermosphere Collective IQVideosHow-to, Visual Tutorials, and MoreResources And LinksIndustry web resources and links DownloadsNewsSuperstoreContact ContactsClose
ECDWorldwide HeadquartersSales RepresentativeLocal Sales Representative
ECD is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the ECD Web site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the ECD website, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
ECD collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. ECD also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by ECD. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This
information is used by ECD for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the ECD Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through ECD public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: ECD
does not read any of your private online communications.
ECD encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from ECD so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. ECD is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the ECD
and ECD family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
ECD collects and uses your personal information to operate the ECD
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. ECD also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from ECD and its affiliates. ECD may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
ECD does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
ECD may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, ECD
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to ECD, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
ECD does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
ECD keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
ECD, in order to determine what ECD services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within ECD to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
ECD Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on ECD or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of ECD; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of ECD, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The ECD Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize ECD pages, or
register with ECD site or services, a cookie helps ECD
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same ECD Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the ECD
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the ECD services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
ECD secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. ECD secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
ECD will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. ECD encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how ECD is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
ECD welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that ECD has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact ECD at jalfonso@ecd.com.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
© ECD, 1996 - 2020. All rights reserved.
Privacy Statement | Terms Of Use
